voiparty.com 2010-11-21

# VOiParty - Generate Residual Income Automatically Using Your Home Phone & Internet

Welcome and Thank You for visiting us at VOIParty.com or the Personal Wedsite of your authorized VOIParty Independent Member ("IM"). The Founders and Management Team of VOIParty believe in leadership by example and creating a friends and family environment, which consist of the people we care about the most. VOIParty has a strong emphasis on integrity and the success of its distributors. Additionally it is our Policy to maintain your personal information confidential. Your Privacy is very important to us and we are committed to protecting and safeguarding it. 

**You may _"Contact Us"_ at: **(239) 945-VOIP (8647) Fax: (239) 471-0738

### E-mail Addresses

**Customer Service:** [customer_service@voiparty.com](mailto:customer_service@voiparty.com?subject=Replying%20From%20Privacy%20Statement)  
**Technical Support:** [support@voiparty.com](mailto:support@voiparty.com?subject=Replying%20From%20Privacy%20Statement)

### Headquarters Address:

4423 Del Prado Blvd South  
Cape Coral, Florida 33904

VOIParty's purpose of providing you with this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information.

VOIParty does not collect personal information about individuals who visit our site except when the information is specifically provided on a voluntary basis.

**The information we collect on our Site generally falls into the following two categories:** Personally Identifiable Information or Aggregate Information

  1. ### Personally Identifiable Information

**This refers to information that lets us know who you are or things specifically about you.**

#### Prospecting Visitors

You may browse our Site without revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. If you want to register or place an order and do not have a sponsoring IM, you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, address, email address, a telephone number) to be shared with an authorized IM near you or a Corporate Sales Representative for the purpose of contacting you, including via email, to assist with registration and ordering. In such event, we might maintain a record of your contact, including such Personally Identifiable Information, in a file specific to you. We use this information to provide better service in the event that you contact us again.

#### Registration

When you register to become an IM and start your own I-commerce business powered by VOIParty, or when you register to shop online as a Customer, enjoying full access to the many products and services available on our Site, we will collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, address, email address, and telephone number). This Personally Identifiable Information is securely stored. You are assigned a VIP/Member Number and select your own password � both are needed to enter the Site and to access your Contact Information.

#### Placing Orders

When you place an order for products or services or a calling plan, we collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, contact and billing information, credit card, and other transaction information). We use this information to deliver your order, process payment, and to communicate with you about the status of your order.

#### Credit Card Information Storage

Credit card information collected at registration or for shopping cart orders/wholesale calling plans is used only to process payment for that specific transaction and, generally, is not retained.

#### Promotions, Training & Surveys

From time to time you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information to complete surveys and questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We use this information to improve our products and services. We may also use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide you newsletters and other marketing information that coincide with your preferences. You may customize your marketing preferences, or let us know if you do not wish to receive any promotional materials.

  2. ### Aggregate Information

This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website that referred you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience.

We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement. 

#### Sharing Your Information

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be stored in our databases.

    1. #### IMs

A business powered by VOIParty, will provide you with advice and information from your own personal business advisory team � a support network consisting of your sponsoring IM and upline organization. To allow such communication, we may share limited contact information with your sponsoring IM and upline organization. They have agreed not to share your information with any non-affiliated third parties, and are obligated to observe the intent of this Privacy Policy. 

    2. #### Customers

In order to assure the highest level of personal service, we may share Personally Identifiable Information about you (excluding credit card information and order details) with your servicing IMs, who are committed to making sure you're pleased with the products you purchase and that you receive a favorable experience. Your servicing IMs have agreed not to share your information with any non-affiliated third parties, and are obligated to observe the intent of this Privacy Policy.

    3. #### General

We may share Personally Identifiable Information with other VOIParty-related entities and/or trusted business partners with whom we collaborate, as well as those that provide services to our Site. When we engage non-affiliated third-party agents or contractors, we require them also to observe the intent of this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Policies and Procedures or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

In the event that VOIParty or its related entities merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or its respective assets be acquired, you should expect that we would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to companies assuming the role of serving you and other users of our Site. 

Your permission is always secured first. We will not use or share the Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information, including those described above, without providing you an option whether to permit any such unrelated uses. 

### Maintaining Your Information

We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise correct Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, you may edit your information online after completing registration, or contact us as described in the "Contact Us" section above. 

### Protecting Your Information

We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.

It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access our Site, and to promptly advise VOIParty or your IM if you ever suspect that your password has been compromised. We strongly encourage you to change your password regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because your VIP/Member Number and password are specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for any and all use of our Site conducted with your identification number and password. 

### The use of Cookies on This Site

A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a website to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. Cookies also enable an Internet retailer like VOIParty to keep track of a consumer's electronic "shopping cart" before completing a purchase. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide us access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you choose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer, Firefox, or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. If you turn off cookies completely, there may be some website features that will not be available to you, and some web pages may not display properly.

To support the personalized features of our Site (such as your country and language codes, electronic shopping cart, and other ordering and browsing functions), we must send a cookie to your computer's hard drive and/or use cookie-based authentication to identify you as a registered Site user. We do not, however, use so-called "surveillance" cookies that track your activity elsewhere on the web. 

### Use of Active-X and JAVA Applets on This Site

Active-X programs and JAVA applets are executable programs that can be transferred to your computer's hard drive to cause your computer to perform functions in connection with your visit to a website. Our Site does transfer Active-X programs or Java Applets to your computer's hard drive. 

### Use of Third-party Media

The VOIParty Site may run limited third-party ads only for those Merchant and Services Partners with whom we link. We will additionally use third-party media and research companies to place ads for us on other parties' websites. 

### Links to Other Websites

Links to third-party websites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional shopping for various other goods and services. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those websites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.

We maintain contractual agreements with all of our Merchant and Services Partners, which require them to observe the intent of this Privacy Policy. When you enter a Partner Store from our Site, we provide them only with your identification number for purposes of introducing you. In return, the Partner Store shares with us any purchases you make from their websites in order for us to assign proper credit to you and to your servicing IM. 

### Children's Privacy Protection

As stated in our Policies and Procedures minors must be of the age of majority in his or her state of residence in order to participate or become an IM. We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents or guardians to be an active participant in their child's online activities. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we discover personal data from a child through our Site, we will eliminate that data. 

### Changes to the Privacy Policies

Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Policy has changed. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. 

**_Updated and effective January 1, 2010._**

_Copyright �2010 VOIParty, Inc._ All rights reserved.
